
# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rake db:seed (or created alongside the db with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   cities = City.create([{ name: 'Chicago' }, question: { name: 'Copenhagen' }])
#   Mayor.create(name: 'Emanuel', city: cities.first)


  Item.create(answer: "1", question: "Gala")
  Item.create(answer: "2", question: "Golden Delicious")
  Item.create(answer: "3", question: "Granny Smith")
  Item.create(answer: "4", question: "Fuji")
  Item.create(answer: "5", question: "Macintosh")
  Item.create(answer: "6", question: "Spartan")
  Item.create(answer: "7", question: "Ginger Gold")
  Item.create(answer: "8", question: "Red Delicious local")
  Item.create(answer: "11", question: "Gala Local")
  Item.create(answer: "12", question: "Gold Delicious Local")
  Item.create(answer: "14", question: "Fuji Local")
  Item.create(answer: "15", question: "Macintosh Local")
  Item.create(answer: "16", question: "Spartan Local")
  Item.create(answer: "17", question: "Red Delicious Local")
  Item.create(answer: "20", question: "Ambrosia")
  Item.create(answer: "22", question: "Pink Lady")
  Item.create(answer: "28", question: "Pacific Rose")

  Item.create(answer: "41", question: "Cherries")
  Item.create(answer: "42", question: "Cherries Rainer")
  Item.create(answer: "45", question: "Cranberries")
  Item.create(answer: "47", question: "Raspberry Local")
  Item.create(answer: "50", question: "BlueBerries")
  Item.create(answer: "51", question: "RaspBerries")
  Item.create(answer: "52", question: "BlackBerries")
  Item.create(answer: "56", question: "StrawBerries Box")
  Item.create(answer: "57", question: "StrawBerries Local")


  Item.create(answer: "70", question: "Mandarin Satsuma")
  Item.create(answer: "71", question: "Mandarin Chinese Loose")
  Item.create(answer: "72", question: "Mandarin Chinese Box")
  Item.create(answer: "73", question: "Mandarin Japanese Loose")
  Item.create(answer: "74", question: "Mandarin Japanese Box")
  Item.create(answer: "75", question: "Mandarin Korean Loose")
  Item.create(answer: "76", question: "Mandarin Korean Box")
  Item.create(answer: "77", question: "Mandarin LoKan")
  Item.create(answer: "78", question: "Mandarin Ponkan Taiwan")
  Item.create(answer: "79", question: "Mandarin Kinnow")
  Item.create(answer: "80", question: "Mandarin Honey")
  Item.create(answer: "81", question: "Mandarin Clementine Loose")
  Item.create(answer: "82", question: "Mandarin Clementine Box")


  Item.create(answer: "101", question: "Grapes Black")
  Item.create(answer: "102", question: "Grapes Green")
  Item.create(answer: "103", question: "Grapes Red")
  Item.create(answer: "104", question: "Grapes Red Globe Seed In")

  Item.create(answer: "121", question: "Orange Navel SM")
  Item.create(answer: "122", question: "Orange Navel LG")
  Item.create(answer: "123", question: "Orange Navel XLG")
  Item.create(answer: "124", question: "Orange Valencia SM")
  Item.create(answer: "125", question: "Orange Valencia LG")
  Item.create(answer: "131", question: "Orange Blue Jay SM")
  Item.create(answer: "132", question: "Orange Blue Jay LG")
  Item.create(answer: "133", question: "Orange Blue Jay XLG")

  Item.create(answer: "151", question: "Tangerine Honey")

  Item.create(answer: "160", question: "Grapefruit Pink SM")
  Item.create(answer: "161", question: "Grapefruit Pink LG")
  Item.create(answer: "164", question: "Grapefruit Pomelo")

  Item.create(answer: "190", question: "Cantaloupe SM")
  Item.create(answer: "191", question: "Cantaloupe LG")
  Item.create(answer: "192", question: "Cantaloupe Cut")
  Item.create(answer: "193", question: "Honey Dew")
  Item.create(answer: "194", question: "Honey Dew Cut")
  Item.create(answer: "197", question: "Watermelon Seedless")
  Item.create(answer: "198", question: "Watermelon Seedless Cut")
  Item.create(answer: "199", question: "Mini-Watermelon Seedless")

  Item.create(answer: "200", question: "Raisin Snap Pack")
  Item.create(answer: "201", question: "Raisin T/S 10oz")
  Item.create(answer: "202", question: "Raisin Frame 10oz")
  Item.create(answer: "204", question: "Dragon Fruit")
  Item.create(answer: "210", question: "Avocado")
  Item.create(answer: "211", question: "Figs Black")
  Item.create(answer: "212", question: "Figs Green")
  Item.create(answer: "213", question: "Figs Brown")
  Item.create(answer: "214", question: "Kiwi Fruit")
  Item.create(answer: "215", question: "Kiwi Fruit Gold")
  Item.create(answer: "217", question: "Papaya Tree-Ripen")
  Item.create(answer: "218", question: "Papaya Hawaii")
  Item.create(answer: "219", question: "Papaya Strawberry")
  Item.create(answer: "220", question: "Dates Dried")
  Item.create(answer: "221", question: "Pinapple")
  Item.create(answer: "222", question: "Pineapple Cut")
  Item.create(answer: "224", question: "Pomegranate SM")
  Item.create(answer: "225", question: "Pomegranate LG")
  Item.create(answer: "226", question: "Star Fruit")
  Item.create(answer: "227", question: "Lychee Nuts")
  Item.create(answer: "228", question: "Longan")
  Item.create(answer: "229", question: "Kumquat")
  Item.create(answer: "231", question: "Mango")
  Item.create(answer: "233", question: "Mango Manila")
  Item.create(answer: "235", question: "Passion Fruit Yellow")
  Item.create(answer: "238", question: "Guava")

  Item.create(answer: "240", question: "Pear Anjou")
  Item.create(answer: "241", question: "Pear Barlett")
  Item.create(answer: "242", question: "Pear Bose")
  Item.create(answer: "243", question: "Pear Brown")
  Item.create(answer: "244", question: "Pear Ya Li")
  Item.create(answer: "245", question: "Pear Korean")
  Item.create(answer: "248", question: "Pear Asian")
  Item.create(answer: "249", question: "Pear Fragrant")

  Item.create(answer: "261", question: "Persimmon Fuyu SM")
  Item.create(answer: "262", question: "Persimmon Fuyu LG")
  Item.create(answer: "263", question: "Persimmon Hachiya SM")
  Item.create(answer: "264", question: "Persimmon Hachiya LG")

  Item.create(answer: "270", question: "Plum Black Local")
  Item.create(answer: "271", question: "Plum Black SM")
  Item.create(answer: "272", question: "Plum Black LG")
  Item.create(answer: "273", question: "Plum Red Local")
  Item.create(answer: "274", question: "Plum Red SM")
  Item.create(answer: "275", question: "Plum Red LG")
  Item.create(answer: "276", question: "Plum Green")
  Item.create(answer: "278", question: "Plum Prune")
  Item.create(answer: "281", question: "Plum Pluot")

  Item.create(answer: "300", question: "Nactarines Local")
  Item.create(answer: "301", question: "Nectarines White")
  Item.create(answer: "302", question: "Nectarines SM")
  Item.create(answer: "303", question: "Nectarines LG")
  Item.create(answer: "304", question: "Peaches Local")
  Item.create(answer: "305", question: "Peaches SM")
  Item.create(answer: "306", question: "Peaches LG")
  Item.create(answer: "307", question: "Peaches White")
  Item.create(answer: "308", question: "Apricots Local")
  Item.create(answer: "309", question: "Apricots")
  Item.create(answer: "311", question: "Peaches Donut")
  Item.create(answer: "312", question: "Peaches White Local")
  Item.create(answer: "313", question: "Nectarines Donut")
  Item.create(answer: "314", question: "Nectarines White Local")

  Item.create(answer: "331", question: "Banana")
  Item.create(answer: "333", question: "Banana Baby")

  Item.create(answer: "336", question: "Lemon")
  Item.create(answer: "338", question: "Lime")
  Item.create(answer: "339", question: "Lime Key")
  Item.create(answer: "7336", question: "Bag Baby Lemons")

  Item.create(answer: "500", question: "Bean Board")
  Item.create(answer: "501", question: "Bean Green")
  Item.create(answer: "503", question: "Bean Yellow")

  Item.create(answer: "531", question: "Cucumber English Long")
  Item.create(answer: "532", question: "Cucumber FSP")
  Item.create(answer: "533", question: "Cucumber Field")
  Item.create(answer: "536", question: "Cucumber Japanese")
  Item.create(answer: "537", question: "Cucumber Mini")

  Item.create(answer: "551", question: "Cauliflower Local")
  Item.create(answer: "552", question: "Cauliflower Cello SM")
  Item.create(answer: "553", question: "Cauliflower Cello LG")

  Item.create(answer: "560", question: "Eggplant")
  Item.create(answer: "561", question: "Eggplant Long")

  Item.create(answer: "571", question: "Lettuce Endive")
  Item.create(answer: "572", question: "Lettuce Head / Iceberg")
  Item.create(answer: "573", question: "Lettuce Green Leaf")
  Item.create(answer: "574", question: "Lettuce Red Leaf")
  Item.create(answer: "575", question: "Lettuce Romaine")
  Item.create(answer: "577", question: "Lettuce Butter")
  Item.create(answer: "580", question: "Lettuce Romaine Heart Bag")

  Item.create(answer: "600", question: "Mushroom White Jumbo")
  Item.create(answer: "603", question: "Mushroom Portabella")
  Item.create(answer: "604", question: "Mushroom Brown")
  Item.create(answer: "605", question: "Mushroom Skitake")
  Item.create(answer: "606", question: "Mushroom Enoki")

  Item.create(answer: "611", question: "Beet Bulk")
  Item.create(answer: "612", question: "Beet Bunch")
  Item.create(answer: "613", question: "Carrot Snap Top")
  Item.create(answer: "614", question: "Carrot Bunch")
  Item.create(answer: "615", question: "Carrot Baby")
  Item.create(answer: "619", question: "Lo Bak / Daikon")
  Item.create(answer: "621", question: "Parsnip")
  Item.create(answer: "622", question: "Radishes")
  Item.create(answer: "625", question: "Turnip Brown")
  Item.create(answer: "626", question: "Turnip White")
  Item.create(answer: "627", question: "Yam")
  Item.create(answer: "630", question: "Carrots 2lbs Bag")

  Item.create(answer: "640", question: "Onion Boiler / Bag")
  Item.create(answer: "641", question: "Onion Cooking")
  Item.create(answer: "642", question: "Onion Green")
  Item.create(answer: "643", question: "Onion Leeks")
  Item.create(answer: "644", question: "Onion Red")
  Item.create(answer: "645", question: "Onion Shallots")
  Item.create(answer: "647", question: "Onion White")
  Item.create(answer: "648", question: "Onion Sweet")

  Item.create(answer: "670", question: "Potato  Bakers") 
  Item.create(answer: "672", question: "Potato Bakers 10 LBs Bag")
  Item.create(answer: "673", question: "Potato Nugget White")
  Item.create(answer: "674", question: "Potato Red")
  Item.create(answer: "675", question: "Potato Sweet")
  Item.create(answer: "676", question: "Potato White")
  Item.create(answer: "678", question: "Potato Yukon")
  
  Item.create(answer: "680", question: "Sprouts Alfalfa")
  Item.create(answer: "681", question: "Sprouts Bean")
  
  Item.create(answer: "691", question: "Artichoke")
  Item.create(answer: "692", question: "Belgium Endive")
  Item.create(answer: "693", question: "Bittermelon")
  Item.create(answer: "695", question: "Kale")
  Item.create(answer: "696", question: "Mo Qua")
  Item.create(answer: "697", question: "Okra")
  Item.create(answer: "698", question: "Rappini")
  Item.create(answer: "699", question: "Radicchio")
  Item.create(answer: "700", question: "Rhubarb")
  Item.create(answer: "701", question: "Steam Noodles")
  Item.create(answer: "702", question: "Tofu Soft / Blue")
  Item.create(answer: "703", question: "Tofu Firm / Red")
  Item.create(answer: "704", question: "Wintermelon")
  Item.create(answer: "705", question: "Chayote")
  Item.create(answer: "706", question: "Red Chard")
  Item.create(answer: "710", question: "Asparagus")
  
  Item.create(answer: "720", question: "Squash Banana Cut")
  Item.create(answer: "727", question: "Squash Zucchini")
  Item.create(answer: "739", question: "Squash Assorted")
  
  Item.create(answer: "740", question: "Herb Assorted")
  Item.create(answer: "750", question: "Herb Anise")
  Item.create(answer: "753", question: "Herb Cilantro")
  Item.create(answer: "756", question: "Herb Garlic")
  Item.create(answer: "757", question: "Herb Ginger")
  Item.create(answer: "761", question: "Herb Parsley")
  Item.create(answer: "762", question: "Herb Parsley Italian")
  
  Item.create(answer: "770", question: "Peas Snow")
  Item.create(answer: "771", question: "Peas English")
  Item.create(answer: "772", question: "Peas Snap")
  
  Item.create(answer: "800", question: "Chop Suey (Mixed Veggi)")
  Item.create(answer: "801", question: "Fruit Salad")
  Item.create(answer: "805", question: "Spring Mix Box")

  Item.create(answer: "821", question: "Corn")
  Item.create(answer: "822", question: "Corn Pack")

  Item.create(answer: "860", question: "Pepper Green")
  Item.create(answer: "861", question: "Pepper Serreno")
  Item.create(answer: "862", question: "Pepper Red")
  Item.create(answer: "865", question: "Pepper Red Hot House")
  Item.create(answer: "866", question: "Pepper Jalepeno")
  Item.create(answer: "868", question: "Pepper Yellow Hot House")
  Item.create(answer: "869", question: "Pepper Orange Hot House")
  Item.create(answer: "879", question: "Pepper Assorted")

  Item.create(answer: "880", question: "Bok Choy Baby")
  Item.create(answer: "881", question: "Bok Choy Green")
  Item.create(answer: "882", question: "Yue Choy")
  Item.create(answer: "883", question: "Gai Lan")
  Item.create(answer: "884", question: "Spinach")
  Item.create(answer: "885", question: "Watercress")
  Item.create(answer: "887", question: "Choy Mue")
 
  Item.create(answer: "906", question: "Broccoli Top")

  Item.create(answer: "918", question: "Celery")
  Item.create(answer: "919", question: "Celery Stalk")

  Item.create(answer: "940", question: "Cabbage Brussels Sprouts")
  Item.create(answer: "941", question: "Cabbage Taiwan")
  Item.create(answer: "942", question: "Cabbage Green")
  Item.create(answer: "943", question: "Cabbage Red")
  Item.create(answer: "944", question: "Cabbage Savoy")
  Item.create(answer: "945", question: "Cabbage Sui Choy")
  
  Item.create(answer: "951", question: "Tomato Strawberry")
  Item.create(answer: "972", question: "Tomato Field")
  Item.create(answer: "973", question: "Tomato H.H. Beefsteak")
  Item.create(answer: "975", question: "Tomato Red On Vine")
  Item.create(answer: "984", question: "Tomatoe Cherry")
  Item.create(answer: "986", question: "Tomato Grape")
  Item.create(answer: "987", question: "Tomato Roma")
  
  Item.create(answer: "991", question: "$1.00 Reduced Items")
  Item.create(answer: "999", question: "Coupon AD")

  Item.create(answer: "5001", question: "Apple Juice")

  Item.create(answer: "3000", question: "Kin's Green Bag")

  Item.create(answer: "1793", question: "Italian Salad")
  Item.create(answer: "1796", question: "Fresh Herb Mix")
  Item.create(answer: "1794", question: "Sweet Baby Lettuce")
  Item.create(answer: "1797", question: "Baby Romaine")
  Item.create(answer: "1795", question: "Baby Arugula")
  Item.create(answer: "1805", question: "Organic Spring Mix")

  Item.create(answer: "628", question: "Long Bulk Beets")
  Item.create(answer: "732", question: "Junior Pumpkin")

  Item.create(answer: "709", question: "Local Black Kale")
  Item.create(answer: "1719", question: "Rainbow Chard")
  Item.create(answer: "746", question: "Organic Local Garlic")
  Item.create(answer: "751", question: "Basil Local")
  Item.create(answer: "759", question: "Thai Basil")
